e-conomic.com 2014-11-21

# e-conomic's online media Privacy Policy

You have signed up with this email address: **$email**

## About the collection, use and protection of your personal data when using e-conomic's online media

When you visit e-conomic's websites, we automatically collect information about your visit. This includes which pages you click on, if you've visited this website before as well as which website or search engine you came from. 

The information we collect from your visit is not personal. In other words, this information cannot be used to identify you personally. We use this information to monitor general tendencies in user behaviour.

In the following, you can read about how we collect information from your visit, why we do it and how your data is protected. 

## Automatically collected data

Every time you visit one or more of [e-conomic's websites](http://www.e-conomic.com/about/online-presence), we automatically collect data about your visit. This includes: 

  * The page you entered first 
  * Whether you have visited the website before 
  * Duration of your visit 
  * Which website you came from 
  * The keyword(s) you entered in the search engine 
  * Which pages you visit

| 

  * The IP address of your visit 
  * Your operating system as well as browser type and version 
  * Your screen resolution and the number of colours used by your PC 
  * Whether your PC supports JavaScript and Flash 
  * Language, country and zone/city

---|---  
  
The data is collected using cookies, the so-called "web beacons" and log files. Most websites collect this type of data, so this is standard practice. 

## Why do we collect data about your visit?

We use the non-personal data from cookies, web beacons and log files to learn how you and other visitors use our websites.

We monitor which pages users consider more or less useful. This helps us to further develop and improve our websites to make them more user-friendly and -relevant.

We use data collected about user behaviour and tendencies both internally and publicly for marketing purposes, e.g. tendency reports based on the figures from the visitor statistics. Such data is collected for all or larger groups of visitors. They do not contain any information which can identify you personally. 

If you are registered as a user of the e-conomic accounting software, cookies are also used to prefill the log-on fields. 

## About the data you enter when ordering a subscription or a trial

When you order a subscription to e-conomic or a trial, you enter your name, e-mail address and other personal data. These data are used to ensure that our system links you with your subscription/trial version.

Moreover, we use your e-mail address to send you information about the use of the accounting software. Your name, e-mail address and personal information will be treated in confidence and will not be disclosed to any third party. 

## About the data you enter on blogs, wikis or forums or when signing up for a news mail

Special rules apply for the use of e-conomic's blogs, wikis, forums and news mails:

**Blogs and wikis  
**When you comment on a post or an article, you enter your name and e-mail address. The name you enter will be shown on your comment. We encourage you to use your real name, even though this is not a requirement.

Your e-mail address will not be shown in public. It will only be used if we need to contact you directly regarding your comment on the blog/wiki.

**Forums  
**Before you can reply to an existing article or author new articles in a forum, you have to register as a user. When you register, you have to enter your user name and your e-mail address.

Like on blogs and wikis, we encourage you to enter your real name as your user name. Your user name will be shown publicly in the forum. Your e-mail address will not be shown publicly and will only be used, if we contact you directly in connection with your forum article.  
**  
IP address registration when using blogs, wikis and forums  
**We register the IP address of your visit on blogs, wikis and forums, when you comment on a forum article. We use the IP address to block any misuse of our websites. It is not used to identify you as a person.

**News mail**  
The e-mail address you enter when you sign up for the e-conomic news mail is only used to send news mails to you.

You can cancel your subscription to the news mail by following the link at the bottom of the e-mail. If you cancel your subscription to the news mail, we will keep your e-mail address to ensure that you will no longer receive news mails from us. 

## How is my personal data protected?

The personal data we collect is stored in a secure environment and treated confidentially. Access to these data is limited to selected e-conomic employees and suppliers.

We do our best to secure your data in the best possible way, but we cannot guarantee the safety of your data, when they are transferred over the Internet. When data is transferred over the Internet, there is a certain risk that others can access them illicitly. In other words, the safety of your data transfer is your own responsibility.

Your data is not disclosed to any third party without your permission, unless legislative authorities require that they be delivered.

**Content which is not protected  
**The content you publish when using our blogs, wikis and forums is publicly available (pictures, text, links, etc.) and is not covered by this declaration of data protection.

As a user, you are responsible for the content you publish. We may decide to remove content published by you on your request, but we maintain our right not to remove already published content.

For further guidelines on publishing content on our websites, please visit our individual sites. 

## Related pages

This picture of a cookie clashes with the huge amount of text on this page :)

**What is a cookie?**

In computer technology, the term "cookie" is used to describe an opaque piece of data.

A cookie is a small file containing information that a website stores permanently on the hard disk of your computer when you visit a website like this one.

This enables the website to recognise your computer when you visit the page again.

The cookie does not give access to personal data about you and cannot be used to trace your identity.

**If you want to opt out of cookies**

You may set your browser to inform you when you receive a cookie, so that you can accept or reject a cookie.

You should, however, be aware that any changes in your browser settings may mean that certain functions on our website no longer work optimally.

**What are web beacons?**

A web beacon is a small transparent graphics file which is called from web sites. 

Web beacons are used in combination with cookies and make it possible to collect data about user behaviour on websites.

**What are log files?**

When you visit e-conomic's websites, technical information about your visit is registered, e.g. your IP address, browser type and language.

This data is saved in log files on the web server. They are used for statistical purposes, for optimisation of the webservers' performance and for troubleshooting.

**What is an IP address?**

Your computer gets a so-called IP address from your Internet provider when it is connected to the Internet.

IP stands for Internet Protocol. An IP address is a unique number and consists of 4 groups of numbers, e.g. 107.34.98.24. The numbers in the IP address are associated with countries, and often also regions and cities.

We may occasionally have to update these guidelines for personal data.

You will find the most recent guidelines on this page.

Changes will not be implemented retrospectively, and no changes will affect our processing of previously collected data.

**Previous versions**

Here you will find links to previous versions of e-conomic's guidelines for personal data: 

  * [Privacy policy for e-conomic's online media before 30 August 2009](http://www.e-conomic.com/about/privacy-policy-before-2009-08-30)

If you have any questions to these quidelines or suggestions for improvement, please contact us at:

**e-conomic international a/s**

Wildersgade 10 B

DK-1408 Copenhagen K

Denmark

E-mail: [info@e-conomic.com](mailto:info@e-conomic.com)

Phone: +45 88 20 48 40
